Hungry human format you have opened the log
knowledge format shadow also and that's all
property what is cipla the numbers on the weekend were
very good and then it had
hydrated on Monday instead of thousand 35 thousand
280 today it crossed that in like two days
its numbers came on Friday the device was
currently doing programs after that a 300 is
on Christmas it is soft smooth and long
today if you want to subscribe your shots movie
then this tank of pharma
they subscribe your descendants
subscribe channel
and
if you are for profit booking on the thigh of English calligraphy market
but my
problem is that till the processing you get
1299 then you should take it from
question India is a condition subscribe
so
please like this
subscribe
2011 you
can subscribe
from loot high or it is fiction call you take
out from 1195 on skin this is Kunwar remember this
is the middle structure and if you look at
it in the last one and a half month there has been a
lot of decline in any side of the market  I did
not participate, let's come now but let's
discuss those toxins, a good momentum was being
created early in the morning but later it lapsed,
lesbian entry NTES, what
is that,
1769, but
I am doing it here in a tax cycle, I will do it
very late, I was
trying to talk on this topic, I have tried to do
some level wallet on jeans top after a long time,
this staff had
never done 10m unwanted till now from 18th July till now,
but today I am doing VAT, Sachin
says in your presence, justice was just checked on this,
today what a reversal custom total has been given
and under which level have you united your looks,
this morning it has participated a lot but
ironing
that today the increase of concern was seen last Wednesday, this was
made from Nainwa around 1820, if
you delete the update a little, then
click there, auto drivers were
visible, if we look at the data of last four days,
apart from that there was a lot of speed also
From the multiple dori formation, these
are almost good signs where public
distribution is there and
then the removal gets unlocked here and in this
way today we have kept our five decades
mushrooming or the trick Datta meeting below the tree,
so it means that somewhere this
retrace that was formed was around 1820, it is
difficult, it is a little bit form in the
lower side, the way the supports are visible,
so I
feel that this corrective should swing from 1730 to around 27 bases, so on a
limit basis, one should
not press long replies here,
but if someone has an existing normals
position, then I feel that a meeting should be made from there,
these are the divine time's garlic
support, I feel that
entry should be done from there, this is a very
substantial rally of local mill, after such formations are going,
so I am drawing secondary moong or
active, there is coordination and
above 1820 it is difficult once the momentum
will be unlocked Vinod Gupta, cut blouse
is the structure in this way
You have to buy only on the corrective of 1735, inside it is from cloves that